[ cicadas chirping ]
[ fly buzzing ]
[ evangelist on TV ] We come together today ...
[ continues indistinct ]
In dark times such as these ,
we must all remember
to look to the Lord for guidance .
Submit yourselves , then , to God .
[ congregation ] Amen .
Resist the Devil ...
- [ congregation murmurs ] - ... and he will flee from you .
| regret to say ,
| know the powers of Satan firsthand .
Our very own daughter was taken by perverts and swindlers ,
- and let fall into a world of sin . - Sheriff .
You oughta come take a look at this .
[ haunting music playing ]
My God !
[ shorts ]
[ ' Love Will Find a Way " by Pablo Cruise playing ]
[ knocking " Shave and a haircut , two bits " ]
[ Wayne ] Go easy on that stuff , will ya ?
You know what they say about too much of a good thing .
Give me some sugar .
[ soft moaning ]
You 're special .
There ain 't nobody else out there like you .
Now giddy up .
Time is money ! Everybody 's waitin ' .
Whoo !
You 're a fucking sex symbol .
[ ' In The Summertime " by Mungo Jerry playing ]
[ gull calling ]
[ engine starts ]
[ " In the Summertime " continues ]
[ birds cawing ]
- [ tuning radio ] - [ DJ ] Highs in the low ...
[ preacher on radio ] America needs Jesus .
[ disco music playing over car radio ]
[ distorted speech playing ]
[ " I Shouda Stayed Home " by Jerry Reed playing on radio ]
[ Bobby-Lynne ] Maxine .
- [ Maxine ] " The Farmer 's Daughters . " " - Oh !
- Hot damn , lookit ! Here I am . - Wow / !
[ Bobby-Lynne ] Hollywood , here we come !
No , ma 'am . We don 't need Hollywood .
These types of pictures turn regular folks into stars .
We 're gonna do it all ourselves .
- Ain 't that right , RJ ? - Yes , sir !
Finally level the playing field for people like us .
| don 't know , Wayne . That sounds an awful lot like what you said
about the topless car wash . Remember that ?
Yeah , and had the IRS not had a goddamn personal vendetta against me ,
- that would 've panned out beautifully . - Uh-huh .
Well , you know I 'm always game .
My American dream is not unreasonable .
| just want a paid-for house with a big old pool
so I can float around with my knees in the breeze and tan these titties .
- [ laughs ] - [ Bobby-Lynne ] What ?
| was dealt a good hand .
People spend a lot of money to look at what God gave me .
- Be a sin not to take care of ' em . - [ Jackson ] Mm .
- Yes , it sure would . - [ giggles ]
What about you , Maxine ?
What 's your American dream ?
- [ music continues playing on radio ] - Hmm .
- [ bell rings ] - [ clucking ]
[ van radio playing , muffled ]
[ Wayne ] Hurry it up ! We aren 't gonna be long in there !
If this kid I picked up from the university
can put it together like he says ,
our days of struggling might soon be over .
We do even half the numbers of Debbie Does Dallas ,
I 'm out of the red for good .
Hell , let 's make a picture a week , then .
- Patience , darlin ' . - I 've been being patient my whole life .
Well , that 's the thing about bein ' patient .
| need to be famous , Wayne .
- Mm-hmm . - I 'm ready for the high life .
I 'm sick and tired of never gettin ' what I want .
Well , you help me keep those jokers in line out there ,
I 'll make sure you get everything your heart desires .
You better have .
| don 't worry no more , Wayne .
| deserve nice things . | have cosmopolitan taste .
- Don 't I know it . - I mean it !
| want the whole world to know my name .
Like Lynda Carter or some shit .
Hey , everyone with a pulse is gonna lust after a piece of Maxine Minx
once they see what you can do .
- You know why ? - [ chuckles ]
Why ?
" Cause you got that X factor .
Fuckin ' - A-right .
Now mosey on over there and grab us some Wonder bread , Wonder Woman .
- [ Maxine ] I don 't like his girlfriend . - You don 't like anybody 's girlfriend .
She hardly says a word , she just stares at everyone .
Well , she 's shy .
Probably ain 't never seen nobody like us before .
People who stare give me the heebie-jeebies .
Better get used to that if you 're gonna be in the movies .
Your little boyfriend 's cute .
You help him with all his films ?
[ chickens clucking ]
Sometimes . Yeah .
Is that your boyfriend ?
Hey , how come we don 't got to film none of this in order ?
Well , once I have it all in the can , | can rearrange it however I want .
No shit .
| actually intend on experimenting a lot with the film 's edit ,
giving it a certain sense of the avant-garde ,
like they 're doin ' in France . It 's classier that way .
And it 's a good trick to disguise the low budget .
All right , let 's slate it .
[ camera rolling ]
And ... hit it !
All right , go ahead and fill ' er up .
[ clattering ]
You know ,
if you tilt the camera up from the nozzle ...
[ camera stops rolling ]
... it 'll look like he 's using his cock .
[ groove music playing ]
See ? I got good sense too .
[ Maxine ] How come we couldn 't do any of this filming in Houston ?
Ain 't they got plenty of farms ?
Well , this county raised property taxes ,
a little bit of cash goes a long way out here .
Most older folks can 't compete with the bigger outfits no more .
We aren 't the only ones trying to make a buck .
[ evangelist on TV ] Kidnappers , murderers , sex fiends ,
all the result of our increasingly secular society .
Besides , it ain 't exactly something | wanna advertise around town .
You know how some people can get when it comes to sex .
Remember what happened in Sodom and Gomorrah .
- Get what we needed ? - [ RJ ] Oh , I got it !
Thanks to help from your truly .
Got my smokes ?
- Yes , goddamn . - I 'm just askin ' .
Hey , if I 'm gonna be havin ' sex for you , I 'm gonna need cigarettes .
How 's the script ?
| don 't know . It 's all right .
Does it matter ?
Hey , I don 't wanna have to wear a hard hat to make a livin ' .
Do you ?
No .
Then don 't you be bringin ' down the vibe of my investments .
Negativity attracts negative results .
Winstons ? ! You know | only smoke Old Golds !
All they had , Bobby-Lynne .
That 's it ! I 'm callin ® my agent !
[ Maxine ] Just get back in the dang van .
[ engine starts ]
[ Bobby-Lynne whines ]
[ ' I Got a Woman " by Andwella playing ]
- [ engine rumbling ] - [ evangelist ] That 's right .
The deviants are already amongst us , waitin ' for our sons and daughters .
So heed dire warnings ,
and repent before it 's too late .
He may be a forgiving God ,
but every man has got his limits .
[ mooing ]
[ brakes squeal ]
[ man speaking indistinctly over van radio ]
Must be a bad wreck .
[ radio DJ ] Y 'all stay safe out there .
I 'll be right back with some more golden oldies
right after this commercial break .
- 93.5 KBQB . - [ honking ]
[ mooing ]
... the 60th anniversary
... take place this Saturday .
Don 't miss your chance to tour the entire state ...
[ retching and gagging ]
- What is it ? - [ Wayne ] Oh , don 't look .
| hate blood and guts .
[ Wayne ] Just when you thought you 'd escaped the slaughterhouse .
- [ Bobby-Lynne ] Yeah . - [ radio ] Now that 's a bonanza !
- Was that the - - - [ Jackson chuckles ]
[ " Too Sweet to Be Forgotten " by Ronnie McFarlin playing ]
[ Wayne ] Well , this is it !
- Our own studio backlot . - [ Bobby-Lynne ] Thank goodness .
- I 'm horny . - [ Jackson ] You 're always horny .
No . Not always .
It 's perfect .
It 's really gonna add a lot of production value .
[ insects chirping ]
[ song continues playing indistinctly over van radio ]
[ haunting music playing ]
[ crows cawing ]
Y 'all stay put while I go handle business right quick .
[ smooching sounds ]
[ sighs ]
This wasn 't what I had in mind when I agreed to help out on your film .
Gotta start somewhere , Lorraine .
RJ , it 's smut !
When did you become such a prude ?
I 'm not .
| just don 't understand why you 're doing all this .
Because it is possible to make a good dirty movie .
[ sniffs ]
[ old man ] Who 's that ?
Yes , sir , it 's Wayne Galleroy . We spoke on the telephone .
[ door opens ]
[ Wayne ] Uh ...
Howard , right ?
You from the County ?
This here 's private property .
Didn 't you see the signs down at the end of the drive ?
Oh , hey , easy , partner .
[ tense music playing ]
[ Bobby-Lynne giggles ]
Somethin 's wrong .
- [ giggle ] - What 'chu talkin ' about ?
[ Howard ] You 're trespassing .
The law says I can shoot .
Sir ... I ain 't from the County .
I 'm from Houston .
We spoke on Tuesday . You remember ?
About y 'all 's boarding house .
Oh , that 's right .
You 're looking for a place to stay .
Well , you never can be too careful with strangers .
You had me pretty nervous there .
It ain 't even loaded .
Most of the time , just waving it around is all it takes .
Oh , yes , sir .
| keep the same thing in my glove box .
[ Jackson ] Wow , that 's one ugly sumbitch .
[ Bobby-Lynne laughs ]
What ? [ chuckling ] He is .
[ van door closes ]
[ haunting music playing ]
[ Wayne ] Hell of a spread you got here !
[ Howard ] We like it .
[ light cough , breathing hard ]
[ coughing and wheezing ]
You all right there , old timer ?
I 'm fine !
[ wheezing ]
[ grunts ]
- She ain 't much . - [ RJ ] She 's gorgeous !
Building was for soldiers during the Civil War .
They never saw any action , though .
What about you ?
You serve ?
Flat feet .
[ Jackson ] I did . Two tours in South Vietnam .
Had enough farmers trying to shoot me for one lifetime .
Know what I mean , Pops ?
- Oorrah . - [ Bobby-Lynne giggles ]
Oh , careful , Howie !
Hot damn , that 's my future fiancée you 're eyeballin ' there !
Been a while since you 've seen anything that nice ?
| don 't recall you mentioning you 'd be bringing all these others .
Now , about that - -
See , your ad said $ 30 , but ...
| threw in a little extra to sweeten the deal .
| hope that 's okay .
| don 't think I like you , Wayne .
In fact ,
| don 't much like the looks of none of y 'all .
And my wife is next door ,
so I would appreciate a little discretion .
| give you my word .
You won 't even know we 're here .
[ Wayne sighs ]
That was some stellar negotiating .
You really do have a knack for business .
You keep jawin ' , towhead , I 'll pull you off the main stage for a month .
Oh , but then , honey , you won 't make no money neither .
How could you just stand there and let him talk about us like that ?
Oh , calm down . Ain 't no need to harsh the mellow .
It 's harmless , he 's just old .
His pecker ain 't probably been hard since before you were born .
I 'd hate people like us then , too .
He don 't know what we 're doing , does he ?
So , church mouse , you do speak .
No . He sure doesn 't .
And I intend to keep it that way .
Now , I wouldn 't want to give the old codger a heart attack .
Would you ?
It 's better to beg for forgiveness than ask for permission .
- You know what I mean ? - [ car engine starts ]
All right .
That 's enough jabberin ' .
| reckon it 's about high time we cut to the chase
and we give the people what they wanna see .
What do you say ?
Fuckin ' finally !
- [ groove music playing ] - [ Bobby-Lynne moaning ]
[ gasping , moaning ]
[ moaning loudly ]
[ bed creaking ]
[ Jackson grunting ]
Okay , now ... Now flip her over .
[ Bobby-Lynne ] Ooh !
- [ moaning resumes ] - [ bed thudding ]
- Oh , yeah ! Fuck me ! - [ grunting ]
- Yeah ! [ moans ] - Fuck !
That 's great . Just scooch your chin up for me .
- [ moaning ] - All right , now slow it all down .
- I wanna see the passion . - Hey , kid .
How about you just point the camera and stay in your lane ?
Let me do the screwing here .
[ Bobby-Lynne laughs ]
[ moaning loudly ]
Yeah ... mm ...
Yes ! [ moaning ]
[ music stops ]
[ muffled Bobby-Lynne moaning ]
[ Bobby-Lynne ] Oh , my God ! [ panting ]
[ distant crow cawing ]
[ water lapping ]
[ birds chirping ]
[ haunting music playing ]
[ bird calling ]
Now I may not know shit from Shinola when it comes to filmmaking ,
but I know for damn sure people are gonna wanna see what I just saw in there .
Well , that 's ' cause I 'm not treating it like pornography , but as cinema .
That 's what these other adult films are lackin ' .
Whatever you 're doin ' , you keep doin ' it .
People 's eyes are gonna pop out of their damn skulls when they see this .
We 're gonna be rich .
Feel how hard my cock is .
[ Wayne exhales ]
[ ' Sexy Eyes " by Dr. Hook playing ]
Oh , sorry , baby .
[ scoffing ]
Don 't be standin ' there , like you 're all proud of yourself .
| was born for this line of work .
Uh , you didn 't do nothin ' , dummy .
It 's called actin ' .
You good , but you ain 't that good .
[ inhales deeply , moaning loudly ]
Fuck my pussy !
Oh , you make me so wet !
Oh , my God , you 're so big !
[ sighs deeply ]
Tsk , aw , don 't look so glum .
You did just fine . Come here .
| think I love you .
Bless your heart .
[ gurgling ]
[ water lapping ]
[ suspenseful music playing ]
[ distant bird screeching ]
[ haunting music playing ]
[ panting ]
[ RJ ] And ... action !
[ groove music playing ]
Sorry to bother you , ma 'am ,
but my van broke down in the highway back yonder ,
and I was hopin ' I could use y 'all 's phone to call for help .
Oh , my goodness !
I 'm afraid we don 't own a telephone ,
but my daddy will be home soon ,
and I 'm sure he can give you a lift to town .
Would you like to ... come inside ?
Much obliged .
[ haunting music playing ]
[ clock ticking ]
[ hinges creak ]
Hello ?
- [ flies buzzing ] - [ water dripping ]
[ suspenseful music playing ]
Lemonade ?
[ metal clanks ]
[ tense music playing ]
[ sighs ] Sure is hot out there .
You must be awful thirsty .
[ chuckles ] Yes , ma 'am .
[ sipping ]
It 's got a good taste .
[ drinks noisily ]
[ clears throat ]
| should probably get back now .
My boyfriend gets real fussy when he don 't know where I 'm at , so ...
[ whispering ] Come with me before Daddy gets home .
| was young once too .
It was taken right before the first war .
Believe it or not , my Howard served in both .
He survived the trenches at Omaha Beach .
There wasn 't anything he wouldn 't do for me back then .
That 's the power of beauty .
| was a dancer in those early years .
But then the war came , so ...
not everything in life turns out how you expect .
Such a special face .
Beautiful .
Look .
[ sighs ]
| don 't know what 's come over me .
I 've never quite felt like this before .
If Daddy catches us ...
there 's no tellin ' what he might do .
What are you doing ?
[ truck approaching ]
You should go .
It will be our secret .
What will ?
Shh .
[ foreboding music playing ]
[ grunting ]
[ percussive music playing ]
Watch out !
I 've been lookin ' everywhere for you !
Sorry .
The kid says we 're gonna lose the light !
Well , come on , now . Chop-chop .
[ thinking ] You 're not gonna end up like them .
[ snorting ]
[ sniffling ]
- You 're a fucking sex symbol . - [ sniffles ]
[ sniffles ]
| will not accept a life I do not deserve .
[ breathing deeply ]
[ sets down bag ]
[ keys rattle ]
[ ominous music playing ]
[ Wayne ] You ready ?
[ groove music playing ]
Let 's go to work .
[ " The Devil Made Me Do It " by Rasputin Stash playing ]
[ Wayne ] Coast is clear .
- [ Lorraine ] Sound speed . - [ RJ ] Right ...
- Okay , we 're rolling . - Farmer 's Daughter , take one .
[ RJ ] Action .
I 'm looking for the owner of this farm .
His daughter said I could find him in here .
You must 've been talkin ' to my sister .
Sister ? She didn 't mention you .
Not surprised .
She 's always been jealous .
I 'm younger , get all the attention .
Daddy never lets her leave the farm anymore .
He 's very protective .
Well , I was hopin ' he can give me a ride back to town before it got dark .
We shouldn 't disturb him .
It would only make him angry .
You wouldn 't like Daddy when he 's angry .
| could give you a ride .
[ ominous music playing ]
[ brush scraping ]
[ groove music playing ]
[ Maxine moaning ]
[ Jackson grunting ]
[ moaning and grunting continue ]
[ moaning ]
[ muffled Maxine moaning ]
[ ominous music playing ]
[ Maxine moaning loudly ]
[ film stops rolling ]
[ soft piano playing ]
[ Howard ] We talked about this .
[ old woman ] Howard ? Please .
You know I can 't .
My heart ... [ groans ]
[ suspenseful music playing ]
[ " Act Naturally " by Loretta Lynn playing ]
J They 're gonna put me in the movies J
S They 're gonna make a big star out of me r
I They 'll make a film about a girl who 's sad and lonely
J And all I gotta do is J
3 Act naturally 3
You were amazing out there .
Now I know why Wayne left his wife for you .
- [ scoffs ] So do I - Careful .
Told y 'all she was somethin ' special .
X factor .
Thanks , baby .
- [ Maxine ] What are you looking at ? - [ Wayne ] Wait , come on , now .
No , Wayne .
Ain 't nobody ever teach you not to stare ?
It 's rude .
- You got somethin ' to say to me or what ? - No .
Well ... I do have a question .
See ? She 's interested , is all .
What 's on your mind , church mouse ?
Isn 't it strange ...
watching her doing it with him ?
It 's just business .
As long as the camera is runnin ' .
[ Lorraine ] So the camera changes things ?
- That 's right . - [ RJ ] It 's not real life , Raine .
It 's just a movie .
| know that .
Just ea yin ' ... what about love ?
What about love ?
Well , don 't y 'all believe in it ?
Of course we believe in love .
How can you love someone and still be with other people ?
You think we don 't have no morals or something .
- Is that it ? - No ! No , I - -
Take it from me , letting outdated traditions
control how you live your life will get you nowhere .
| don 't know about you , but I got better places to be than where I came from .
- Amen to that . - [ Maxine ] And besides , it 's just sex .
You can decide who you wanna love , but not who you wanna screw .
Attraction is out of our control .
It ain 't healthy keeping those feelings locked away inside .
| seen you sneaking a few long peeks at Jackson over here .
- No , I ... I wasn 't looking ... - [ Bobby-Lynne ] It 's okay .
He don 't mind none .
She 's right . I don 't mind .
No offense .
[ Bobby-Lynne ] Everybody likes sex .
It 's a gas .
We 're just not afraid to admit it .
Queer , straight , Black , White ...
[ scoffs ] It 's all disco .
You know why ?
Because one day , we 're gonna be too old to fuck .
And life 's too short , if you ask me .
Roger that .
The fact of the truth of the matter is , we turn folks on .
- And that scares ' em . - They can 't look away neither .
That 's right .
- We 're like a foxy car wreck . - [ Wayne chuckles ]
[ Wayne ] Which is how I know
that this new home video market is set to explode .
Finally , people are gonna get to see what they desire
in the privacy of their own homes , free of judgment .
We 're gonna give that to them before anyone else .
Porn ain 't only gonna be for perverts no more .
Aw . Toast to the perverts .
They 've been pa yin ' our bills for years .
Hear , hear ! To the perverts !
To livin ' a life of excess ,
being young and having fun till the day we die .
To the power of independent cinema .
To living life on our own terms .
And never accepting what self-righteous naysayers have to say .
[ Wayne ] Right on .
| don 't know if I agree with all of that ...
but I did like what I saw today .
| didn 't think I would , but I did .
[ Wayne ] Cheers to that .
- [ Jackson ] You ready ? - Yeah .
[ playing " Landslide " ]
J I took my love , I took it down
3 I climbed a mountain and I turned around
3 And I saw my reflection
J In the snow-covered hills I
3 Till the landslide brought me down
J Oh , mirror in the sky , what is love ?
I Can the child within my heart rise above ? J
J Can I sail through the changin ' ocean tides ? I
Can I handle the seasons
J Of my life ?
Mm-mm-mm , mm-mm $
Mm-mm , mm-mm-mm $
J Well , I 've been afraid of changin 'd
3 ' Cause I built my life around you §
g But time makes you bolder I
J Even children get older J
J And I 'm gettin ' older too F
S Mm-mm $
[ song ends ]
| wanna do a scene in the movie .
What ?
| wanna be in the movie .
No .
Well , why not ?
[ scoffs ] Well ...
Because ... no .
Did y 'all put her up to this or somethin ' ?
- [ Bobby-Lynne ] No ! - Hey !
Take it easy . They didn 't do nothin ' .
Nobody put me up to anything . I 've been thinking about it all day .
And ...
Well , I 'm young .
And if we really are makin ' a good dirty movie ,
then I don 't wanna just carry the equipment .
| wanna be in it .
Well , you can 't .
Says who ?
It 's my film , Lorraine .
| mean , it wouldn 't make any sense .
We 've already shot half of it .
The story can 't just suddenly change midway through .
Why ?
Because it just isn 't done .
What about in Psycho ? You love that movie .
Well , Psycho is a horror film .
And that plot was a MacGuffin to build suspense .
And I 'm not making that kind of movie .
[ Lorraine ] Oh , come on , RJ . Nobody 's comin ' to see this film for the plot .
They 're comin ' to see tits and ass .
- And a big dick . - Lorraine !
- [ all snickering ] - It 's the truth .
Why not just give the people what they 're pa yin ' for ?
Because I 'm making something better than that .
When did you become such a prude ?
[ Wayne ] All right , hold on .
| am the executive producer , which means I get a word .
So , why don 't we just take a step outside
before anythin ' gets said that someone might regret ?
You gotta back me up in here , Wayne !
| mean , this situation is fixin ' to get outta control .
- It is awfully close . - Relax .
Hey , what is it they say , " Life imitates art " ?
It 's the other way around .
Well , whatever , it don 't matter . But you need to listen to me , okay ?
Because you ain 't been 42 , and I have been 23 .
And I 'm gonna explain somethin ' to you about young women .
Now , if she 's serious ...
which I suspect she is ...
she 's gonna do it whether you like it or not .
Now , you try to stop her , not only is she gonna do it ,
she 's gonna go on and do it with God knows how many people
in God knows how many other films , and nobody wants that .
The way I see it , you only got one good option here .
What , letting her get balled by some man-whore ?
Come on now ! Jackson is a professional .
He ain 't got no diseases or nothin ' .
You just want more sex in the movie .
That ain 't me , hoss . She wants it , you heard her .
Heck , if she does great , she gets famous , maybe she 'll take you with her .
Wayne , you don 't get it .
Lorraine is not like the others in there .
She is a nice girl .
| beg your pardon ?
No , I didn 't mean it like that .
Oh , I hate to be the one to tell you this ...
but ain 't none of them nice girls .
[ distorted groove music playing ]
[ haunting music playing ]
[ crickets chirping ]
[ water running ]
[ sobbing softly ]
[ sighs in frustration ]
To hell with this . She can have it .
- Let 's see how far they get without me . - [ engine starting ]
Good luck finding your own way out of here .
[ ' Don 't Fear the Reaper " by Blue Oyster Cult playing over radio ]
What the ...
Ma 'am ?
Are you all right ?
Sorry , I 'm ...
[ old woman moans ]
Ma 'am ?
[ stammering ]
What ?
How come you just did that ?
Why won 't you look at me ?
Look at me like you looked at her .
What ?
| can show you what I 'm capable of .
Stop . I don 't wanna see it .
Maybe we should just go find your husband .
[ grunts ]
[ chokes and gasps ]
[ ' Don 't Fear The Reaper " continues playing over van radio ]
[ continues choking and gasping ]
Help me .
[ RJ choking , gasping ]
[ coughing and gurgling ]
[ old woman grunting angrily ]
[ continues grunting angrily ]
[ wailing ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ " Oui Oui Marie " by Chelsea Wolfe playing ]
[ ' Don 't Fear the Reaper " by Blue Oyster Cult resumes playing ]
[ door opens ]
[ music stops ]
RJ ?
[ haunting music playing ]
- [ gasps ] - Hey , hey , hey .
What 's goin ' on , church mouse ?
[ breathing heavily ] It 's RJ .
| woke up , and he was gone . I ...
You don 't think he left me , do you ?
Well , the van 's still here .
He 's gotta be around somewhere .
Oh , hey , it ain 't like your dog ran off .
He 's probably just processin ' things , you know ?
Go on back to bed .
I 'd feel bad if I hurt him . | don 't wanna break up .
Hun , you didn 't do nothin ' wrong .
He 'll get over it .
He just needs to toughen up , is all .
Come on . I 'll talk to him in the morning .
Will you help me find him ?
[ exhales ]
Please ? I 'm worried .
All right .
| ain 't gettin ' in the middle of no more of this shit .
[ Wayne , whispering ] RJ !
Are you in here , brother ?
This ain 't the way to go about handlin ' this .
- [ door opens ] - [ softly ] Oh , no .
[ stammers ] I 'm sorry if I disturbed you .
[ Howard ] What are you doin ' out here ?
I 'm lookin ' for my boyfriend .
Have you seen my wife ?
No , sir .
[ Wayne ] Two keys to keepin ' a healthy relationship .
Never let a good woman out of your sight .
Never mention her weight .
How do you think I 've been surrounded
by so many beautiful females my whole life ?
There 's an art to it .
Just like business .
- [ yells ] - [ cow moos ]
- Fuck ! Son of a bitch ! - [ mooing continues ]
[ grunting and groaning ]
Oh , fuck me !
[ cows mooing loudly ]
Oh , shut up , cheeseburger ! Go wander into traffic .
[ groaning ] Oh , fuck .
[ breathing heavily ]
RJ , you in here ?
| stepped on a nail .
Come on out and help me , for Christ 's sake !
I 'm gonna catch tetanus from this shit .
[ groans ]
RJ ?
Church mouse , that you ?
[ groaning ]
[ grunting ]
There 's another light down in the cellar .
Can you go get it ?
Please . My wife is not well .
It 's very dark , and I 'm worried she could fall and break her hip .
[ door opens ]
Downstairs . You 'll see my workbench .
[ footsteps rustling ]
[ Lorraine sighs ]
Found it !
Hey , I 'm locked in !
Hey !
[ door rattling ]
Hey ! Hey ! Open up !
[ panting ]
[ screaming ]
[ crying ]
[ door creaking ]
What is it , baby ?
Thought I heard somethin ' .
Probably nothin ' .
Old habits die hard .
Go back to sleep .
Aye , aye , captain .
[ footsteps approaching ]
[ door creaking ]
Everything okay , Pops ?
My wife , she 's gone missing .
Missin ' ?
She gets confused .
It happens sometimes after dark .
Lot of firepower for a missin ' wife .
It 's for gators .
| found her once by the edge of our pond .
If she was to fall in ...
Want some help ?
Not for self , but for country , right ?
Let me go and get my skivvies .
[ ominous music playing ]
[ haunting music playing ]
[ Jackson ] I say we each take a side of the perimeter .
Cover ground quicker that way .
[ Howard ] I only got the one light .
No offense ,
but it 's been a while since you was deployed .
| spent three nights face down in a rice paddy
scanning for land mines and trip wires .
Once a Marine , always a Marine .
If she 's out here ...
I 'll find her .
[ haunting music continues ]
[ breathing heavily ]
| ain 't got nothin ' , Pops .
Shit .
What you doing all the way in there ?
[ water sloshing ]
Oh , no .
Pops , you okay ? You in here ?
[ Lorraine , crying ] Help ! Help , somebody , please !
Please help me !
RJ !
Help !
[ Lorraine sobbing ]
[ breathing heavily ]
[ sobbing and panting ]
Oh , shit !
[ panting ] You scared me , Pops .
Once a Marine , always a Marine .
Well ...
Your lady ain 't in there .
| can 't give her what she wants anymore .
You don 't understand what it 's like .
You can still do as you please .
Say what ?
The last bohemian that stayed here was the same .
Traipsin ' around in barely any clothes ,
enticin ' my wife .
Yeah ... Okay .
Well , we better get back up to the house and find out what 's goin ' on .
| know exactly what 's goin ' on .
[ water splashes ]
[ grunts softly ]
[ screaming ]
- [ gasps ] - [ Maxine continues screaming ]
[ gasps ]
- [ Maxine continues screaming ] - Maxine ?
That woman was in my bed touching me !
[ crying and screaming ]
You 're just makin ' things worse .
Help me !
Somebody ! Please !
Nobody is comin ' for ya .
Get back down in that cellar and be quiet !
[ sobbing ]
- Shut up ! - Help !
- Hey ! Somebody , please ! - Kidnappers , murderers ,
sex fiends ,
- lurkin ' where we least expect ... - [ Lorraine ] Help !
- Somebody , help ! - ... in good Christian homes ,
right under our very noses !
[ snorting ]
[ exhales ]
[ sniffling and sighing ]
[ Bobby-Lynne ] Jackson ?
Wayne ? Where are y 'all ?
[ sighs ]
Oh , my goodness .
Ma 'am ?
Ma 'am ? Be careful !
Step away from the edge , it 's dangerous .
- [ old woman moans ] - It 's all right . Here , here .
You 're safe now , okay ?
Are you hurt ? I don 't see anything .
My nana gets confused sometimes as well .
| learned all about it .
Believe it or not , I 've even thought about becomin ' a nurse one day .
So ... Okay . Why don 't you come with - -
Oh !
What the hell did you do that for ?
| don 't need a nurse .
Why should you get to have it all ?
What have you ever done , except be a whore ?
Okay , you know what ?
You don 't want my help ? No problem .
| was just tr yin ' to be nice .
You don 't deserve to be able to just flaunt it in my face like you do .
It ain 't my fault you didn 't live the life you wanted .
Now move out of the way , please .
Move ! You mean , old , ugly b - -
Bitch .
[ screaming ]
[ muffled screaming ]
[ screaming stops ]
Was that the one ?
You know I don 't like blondes .
[ groans softly ]
Disgustin ' .
Lorraine ?
RJ ?
[ Howard wheezing ]
[ Howard ] Uh , the place is empty .
What about that other fella , Wayne ?
In the barn . Stuck like the pig he was .
Well , that 's three down .
Four .
And I got another kept up at the house for you .
| don 't want her . This one was different .
She had something special . Like I did .
Sick and tired of never gettin ' what I want .
You know I want to give it to you , Pearl .
But I 'm tired , too .
| know .
[ sighs ]
Tell me I 'm special .
Of course you are .
I 've felt that way since the first moment we met .
You were the most beautiful woman I 'd ever seen .
Oh , not anymore .
Always .
Tell me I 'm yours .
That you still want me .
Make me feel young again .
- What if my heart can 't take it ? - It can .
[ Howard and Pearl kissing ]
[ Pearl moaning ]
[ haunting music playing ]
- [ Howard gasps ] - [ bed creaking ]
[ Pearl moaning ]
- [ Pearl ] Fuck me , Howard . - [ grunts loudly ]
[ Pearl ] Fuck me .
[ Pearl moaning loudly ]
Fuck me .
[ Maxine panting ]
[ Lorraine , screaming and crying ] Help !
Help ! Somebody help me , please !
[ singing indistinctly ]
[ panting ]
[ indistinct singing on TV continues ]
[ crying ] Let me out of here !
Keep your voice down .
Don 't tell me to be quiet ! | was locked in a dungeon down there !
These old people are fucking crazy !
| have to get out of this house before they kill me too .
We need to find the keys to their truck .
| never should have listened to you .
This is all your fault !
Lorraine , we need to stick together .
| hate you !
| hate you all so much !
Lorraine !
[ Howard ] I told her to stay in the damn cellar !
[ Pearl ] That 's all right .
We don 't need her anymore .
We got each other again .
[ Howard ] Help me drag her body inside .
If she 's in the house , that 's self-defense .
- That 's the law . - [ panting ]
[ Pearl ] You don 't really believe anyone 's gonna come looking for ' em , do you ?
[ Howard ] We ain 't gonna risk it .
We need to play this smart , Pearl .
No sense in making a mess now .
If nobody shows up by tomorrow ,
we 'll take the body and we 'll dump her in the pond with the others .
Which reminds me , we 're gonna need to get Wayne outta the barn
- and sink him , too . - [ breathing shakily ]
[ door creaking ]
[ indistinct singing over TV continues ]
She 's heavier than she looks .
- [ gurgles ] - [ gasps ]
Howard . Howard !
Howard ?
Howard !
Where are the keys to the truck ?
- He 's having a heart attack . - I don 't give a shit !
- Where are the fucking keys ? - Well , now ...
- In the kitchen , under the lamp . - ... here we all are
together .
Howard ?
We have reached a crossroads
with salvation ...
- Howard ? - ... or damnation .
You 're gonna rot when people find out what you 've done .
- [ evangelist on TV ] The time is now . - What I have done ?
For if we do not take control of our own fate ...
- What about you ? - ... the Lord shall do it for us .
You don 't think I know who you really are ?
| saw what you did in the barn .
You 're a deviant little whore .
We 're the same .
You 'll end up just like me .
Time to turn our backs on sin and make the commitment ...
I 'm nothin " like you .
... once and for all .
You 're a kidnappin ' , murderin ' sex fiend .
I 'm a fucking star !
The whole world is gonna know my name .
| want to hear you all . Say it with me now .
| will not accept a life I do not deserve .
I will not accept a life I do not deserve .
- Hallelujah ! - [ applause on TV ]
Stop fuckin ' starin ' at me !
[ gun clicks ]
[ gun clicking ]
[ indistinct singing on TV ]
[ breathing heavily ]
Now , that 's what I call divine intervention !
The Lord smiles on those who accept Him .
Praise His name !
Glory be to Jesus !
My hip ... [ gasps ]
Help .
Shh !
[ Pearl ] You whore !
You 're not innocent !
- You 're not special ! - [ engine starts ]
It 'll all be taken from you !
Just like it was from me !
- I 'll tell everyone what you are ! - [ engine revs ]
[ screams ]
It 'll be our secret .
Divine intervention .
[ sniffing ]
Praise the fuckin ' Lord .
[ evangelist ] I hope that , through my own admission ,
others may find the light .
| wanna show y 'all somethin ' .
Get a shot of this .
There she is .
My beautiful little daughter Maxine .
Lured into a life of sin by the very deviants
we warn of here on a daily basis .
From our lovin ' home into the hands of devils .
We pray , one day ,
she 'll find her way home to us .
[ congregation ] Amen .
[ evangelist ] Bless you , bless you .
[ crow cawing ]
[ deputy 1 ] What do you reckon happened , Sheriff ?
How the hell should I know ?
[ deputy 2 ] Hey , boss .
One of the boys found this inside .
What do you think is on it ?
Well , by the looks of everythin ' ...
I 'd say one goddamn fucked up horror picture .
[ ' Bad Case of Loving You ( Doctor , Doctor ) " by Robert Palmer playing ]
[ haunting music playing ]